<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 01:32:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mining on a Raspberry PI4</title>
      <link>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 01:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/mining/</guid>
      <description>I have an extra Raspberry Pi4 doing basically nothing, and with the Nano R4S on its way to replace my router I&amp;rsquo;d soon have 2 Pi4 doing nothing, so until I find a purpose for them, why not get them to mine a bit! I&amp;rsquo;ve been a huge fan of Monero, I like everything of it, from the name (in Esperanto, a language that I have been slowly trying to learn) to its superb privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Slackware on a Raspberry PI4</title>
      <link>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/sarpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 20:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/sarpi/</guid>
      <description>I believe ARM architecture to be the future; and while I wait for the Khadas VIM3 to arrive I thought it may be a good idea to see if the Raspberry Pi could replace my desktop (I hope to achieve that with the VIM3). My Linux distribution of choice is Slackware, one of the many reasons that I like it for, is that you get a sort of two distros in one: It can be a rolling distribution (just like Arch Linux) or a fixed one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging workflow</title>
      <link>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/blogging-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 18:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/blogging-workflow/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to figure out the best workflow for me, for now I&amp;rsquo;m using Emacs with Org mode, the package that generates the Markdown from the org files is called ox-hugo. I&amp;rsquo;m using the development version of Spacemacs and the installation was super easy. My configuration looks like this:
dotspacemacs-configuration-layers &amp;#39;( (org :variables org-want-todo-bindings t org-enable-hugo-support t) ) All the posts (blogs entries) are in one file, as recommended by ox-hugo, each entry is a todo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 22:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://manuel-arguelles.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>First post! I&amp;rsquo;ve finally decided to return to blogging, or at least to give it a try. The idea is to document my ideas, projects and failures.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be using Hugo to generate the site and GitHub&amp;rsquo;s pages to host it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
